CHRISTOPHER "CJ" JOHNSON

UX/UI Designer

CONTACT

✓ Johnsonce3101@gmail.com

A Knoxville, TN

in My Profile

My Portfolio

SKILLS

Design Psychology Front End -

Figma Web Development

Wireframes HTML

Prototyping CSS

User Research JavaScript (JS)

Sketching Node.js

Data Synthesis Git

Usability Testing Bootstrap

Journey Mapping Material UI

UI Design React.js

Adobe Creative Angular.js

EDUCATION

UX/UI Design (Cert.)

V School

OCT 2022 - Current

Web Development (Cert.)

DigitalCrafts

APR 2021 - OCT 2021

Intelligence & Technology (A.A.S)

Community College of the Air-force

JUL 2015 - DEC 2016

Psychology (B.A.)

(Clinical)

East Tennessee State University

AUG 2010 - MAY 2015

PROFILE

A passionate professional who balances combining elements of psychology, and design thinking to create products that fulfill the user's needs. Capable team player with an equal ability to take initiative and lead in order to get the job done. UX Researcher exploring user needs, pain point and behaviors.

EXPERIENCE

Application Development Analyst

Accenture (10/2021 - 10/2022)

- Developed RICEFW solutions for client stakeholders using agile methodologies.
 - Provided timely data analysis for 10k+ defects to improve productivity
- Certified in Salesforce (SF) Platform (Vlocity OmniStudio Developer & Consultant).

Brand Strategist

NueWay Studios (08/2019 - 04/2020)

- First point of contact for clients, guided clients through initial on boarding processes and branded marketing strategies.
- · Elevated customer experience engagement strategy
 - · lead to 50% contract signing increase.

All-Source Intelligence Technician

U.S. Air-Force (07/2015 - 07/2019)

- Assessed vulnerabilities of DoD cyberspace enterprise that could be exploited by adversaries.
- Reduced product completion from 3 months to 48 days.
- Conducted database research prepared intelligence reports and charts.
- Supervision
 - Team lead: Trained supervisors and co-worker on critical thinking, analytical writing skills, and presentation.
 - Trained team members of the importance of resilience.
 - Emphasized organization of documentation regarding product research.